If you have a stem cell, the germarium, in females, will appear to
如果你有一个生殖干细胞，在女性体内，卵原细胞巢将会出现，以
form what are called homocytes,
形成我们所说的卵原细胞，
the basis of a system, and the exact word to use, it means that it
一个系统的基础，而需要使用的确切词汇，这意味着它会
cleaves, cleavage.
卵裂。
So you imagine a cell, it will form two cells, but a stronger, more developed one.
所以你们可以想象一个细胞，它会形成两个细胞，但其中一个更完善，
stronger.
更强壮。
And we will see that from this small cell, a large...
我们将会看到，从这个小细胞中，将会出现一个大的...
of cells. And this cell, if you look at it, it's a collection of cells
细胞群。而这个细胞，如果你仔细观察，它是一个
it's a collection of cells
细胞集合，
through this cleavage, we see a large cell appearing here which will be the
通过这种卵裂，我们看到这里出现一个大的细胞，它将是
oocyte and
卵母细胞，以及
cells around it called follicular cells and larger
周围的细胞，我们称之为卵泡细胞，以及一些
cells here called nurse cells.
这里更大的细胞，我们称之为滋养细胞。
So we start with the germarium.
所以我们最终得到，最初的卵原细胞巢。
A stem cell becomes many cells, I have very small cells around it called follicular cells,
一个干细胞变成许多细胞，我
I have very small cells around it called follicular cells,
有周围非常小的细胞，我们称之为卵泡细胞，
and then I have large accompanying cells called nurse cells.
然后我有一些大的伴随细胞，我们称之为滋养细胞。
One comes from the germline, the other from the somatic line.
其中一个来自生殖系，另一个来自体细胞系。
Some come from my germline, from my mother, some come...
有些来自我的生殖系，来自我的母亲，有些来自...
from the developmental force of the nurse cells.
滋养细胞的发育力量。
Nurse cells and follicular cells release small molecules.
滋养细胞和卵泡细胞释放小分子。
This is my largest cell which will become the oocyte.
这是我最大的细胞，它将成为卵母细胞。
Around it, here, I have cells that will form the nurse cells.
在这里周围，我有一些细胞将形成滋养细胞。
All around, here, I will have cells called follicular cells.
在这里最外围，我将会有一些细胞，我们称之为卵泡细胞。
The nurse cells.
滋养细胞。
And the follicular cells release small
而卵泡细胞释放小的
molecules.
分子。
And these small molecules will go and
而这些小分子将会去
arrange themselves in the cytoskeleton of
排列在...的细胞骨架中
the oocyte.
卵母细胞中。
So they come.
它们来了。
and arrange themselves in
并排列在
specific axes in the form of concentration.
特定的轴线上，形成集中。
In other words, if I put you all over there,
换句话说，如果我把你们都放在那边，
the metabolic concentration will be greater over there than
那边的代谢集中度会比
over here.
这边更高。
Here, to me.
在这里，对我而言。
That will form what is called the flag of high.
它会形成我们所说的“高点标志”。
And what will it do? It will have a concentration like that.
它会做什么？它会像这样形成一个集中。
If I have a concentration, it means I have a plus, and therefore I have a minus.
如果我有一个集中，就意味着我有一个正极，因此我有一个负极。
It will do the same thing in another axis called the apico-caudal axis.
它会在另一个轴线上做同样的事情，我们称之为顶尾轴。
This means that the oocyte, in its development, polarizes itself.
这意味着卵母细胞在其发育过程中会极化。
It has created axes of concentration of force.
它创造了力的集中轴线。
to capture this electromagnetic concentration.
以捕捉这种电磁集中。
So it is oriented within itself.
因此它在内部是定向的。
When we look at a nucleus, a cell,
当我们观察一个细胞核，一个细胞时，
we see that the cell has two large centers.
我们会看到细胞拥有两个主要的中心。
A pure cellular center, with the nucleus,
一个纯粹的细胞中心，带有细胞核，
and a structural center,
以及一个结构中心，
with what are called centrioles, and the...
带有我们所说的中心粒，以及...
What are called microtubules.
我们所说的微管。
The cell will cleave, multiply.
细胞会分裂，增殖。
There is a participation of the structural center and a participation of the cellular center.
有结构中心的参与，也有细胞中心的参与。
Here, it will be the release in the form of my DNA, in the form of
在这里，它将以我的DNA形式释放，以
photocopy.
影印件。
I can never take books out of the library.
我永远不能把图书馆的书拿出去。
I can make copies.
我可以制作它们的副本。
And here, there will be a...
而在这里，将会有一个...
Do you remember in...
你们还记得在...
we had what is called
我们有我们所说的
the equatorial plate
赤道板
with these small images
带着这些小图片
these two small things
这两个小东西
and then it did like that
然后它就变成这样了
and then the mixture around
然后周围的混合物
and then it did this
然后它就形成了这个
well it starts from there
嗯，它就是从那里开始的
you will have to keep that in mind
这一点你们需要记住
in our work
在我们的工作中
we will try to follow
我们将尝试去追踪
to follow
去追踪
the polarity
极性
at each stage
在每个阶段
it will be present
它都会存在
but in a different form
但以一种形式
different. I take a cell, I
不同。我取一个细胞，我
put a nucleus, I have an environment, I
放一个细胞核，我有一个环境，我
have a compartment
有一个区室
extracellular, intracellular, a nucleus, a membrane and
细胞外、细胞内、一个细胞核、一个细胞膜和
a space. We will talk in the field
一个空间。我们将在该领域讨论
of development about what we have.
我们所拥有的发展。
To understand all the development of embryos in a specific process, we will
为了理解胚胎在特定过程中的所有发育，我们将
talk about what is called a metabolic field.
讨论我们所说的代谢场。
What is a metabolic field?
什么是代谢场？
It is a space in which the cell
它是一个细胞在其中
evolves.
演变的空间。
It is a structural space.
这是一个结构空间。
Let's go back.
我们再回顾一下。
Autocrine communication.
自分泌通讯。
I'm in...
我正在...
the street and I absolutely have to pee. I have a device to do crime, I pee,
街上，我必须小便。我
I have a device to do crime, I pee,
有一个用来犯罪的装置，我小便，
but at that moment, there's a strong gust of wind. Everything comes back
小便，但就在那时，刮起一阵大风。一切都吹了回来
on my pants.
到我的裤子上。
I feel the warmth, autocrine communication. We
我感到温暖，自身分泌式通讯。我们
are going to pee together in the bush,
一起去灌木丛中小便，
but the wind is very strong again.
但风又变得非常强劲。
Communication, paracrine, everything comes on you.
通讯，旁分泌，一切都吹到你身上。
I peed in the gutter, do you say that where you are, a gutter?
我在水沟里小便了，你们那里也叫水沟吗？
I pee in the gutter, and it flows.
我在水沟里小便，它就流走了。
You play marbles, hop, and communication, it's in the circulatory system, the gutter.
你玩弹珠，咻，然后通讯，这
it's in the circulatory system, the gutter.
是在循环系统里，水沟。
So it will be endocrine.
所以这将是内分泌。
Now what is neurocrine communication?
那么，什么是通讯呢？
Neurocrine. It's like paracrine communication, but at a distance. I take
神经分泌。这就像旁分泌通讯，但距离较远。我拿
a cell, I pee on myself. I take two cells, I
一个细胞，我对自己小便。我拿两个细胞，我
pee on my neighbor. I take a cell, I go into a gutter and
对我的邻居小便。我拿一个细胞，我去水沟里，然后
I touch another one over there.
我在那里接触到另一个。
Endocrine communication. Now I have a cell here, and the neuronal cells,
内分泌通讯。现在我有一个细胞，在这里，和神经元细胞，
what do they do? They create a large axon.
它们做什么？它们形成一个大的轴突。
we have close communications
我们有近距离通讯
and distant communications
和远距离通讯
telocrine means distant
远距分泌意味着远距离
and then we still have just
然后我们还有
tacrine, but well, I'll explain that
触分泌，但是，那个我再解释
if I'm at a cell here
如果我在这里有一个细胞
we will explain
我们将解释
what is the introduction
什么是引入
of a field
一个场
metabolic. He ate sauerkraut twice. I
代谢的。他两次都吃了酸菜。我
am here in the sauerkraut corner
我在这里，有点不舒服。
and I need to degas a bit. Someone who comes in here into the room doesn't
我需要稍微释放一下。有人走进这个房间，他不会
see, they know right away
看不到，他立刻就知道
where my metabolic field is. There
我的代谢场在哪里。那里有
is a space around me that appears in which there
我周围出现了一个空间，其中有
are small
有一些小的
and which are present in a field around me, because
并且存在于我周围的一个场中，因为
after that it will structure itself, it will organize itself, it
之后它会结构化，它会组织起来，它会
will become more complex.
变得复杂。
Differentiation, change of position, change of form and change
分化，位置改变，形态改变和
of structure and function, that is differentiation.
结构和功能，这就是分化。
Two functions, two different forms. The form is different.
两种功能，两种不同的形态。形态是不同的。
The word biodynamic that must be understood is bio, which means life, and
需要理解的“生物动力学”这个词，“生物”意味着生命，而
dynamic, the dynamic of life in its development.
“动力学”，是生命在其发展中的动力学。
So that's important.
所以这很重要。
In this concept, there is a Blechmidt who talks about metabolic fields.
在这个概念中，有一位Blechmidt谈到了代谢场。
And he talks about different metabolic fields.
他谈到了不同的代谢场。
But to open the introduction and to understand what a metabolic field is,
但为了展开介绍并理解什么是代谢场，
you used the right word, you told me I don't understand the difference between this metabolic field,
你用对了词，你告诉我我不明白这个代谢场之间的区别，
and the environment, and I tell you that's it, it's an environment around
和环境，那么我告诉你，这就是，它是一个周围的环境
but which will
但它会
structure itself and I will explain that little by little so I am there like that and I am and
结构化，我将一点一点地解释，所以我就是这样在这里，我就是
a space
一个空间
around me and as long as I am in this space everything is fine at some point
在我周围，只要我在这个空间里，一切都很好，在某个时刻
there is a border
有一个边界
I touch the borders
我触及边界
Two marks appear.
出现了两个标记。
There's an impulse behind it that makes it change.
后面有一个冲动，导致它发生变化。
And then I have a border that's a bit more annoying.
然后我有一个有点麻烦的边界。
It's a border here.
这是一个边界。
Well, not more annoying, it's a border on which,
最后，这并非更令人困扰，这是一个边界，在此之上，
if I go a little further, I cause a differentiation.
如果我再深入一点，我就会引起分化。
First, I cause a multiplication,
首先，我引起增殖，
and then a multiplication with a differentiation.
然后是增殖伴随分化。
It will depend on the impact that I...
这将取决于我所施加的冲击...
have in my spatio-temporal space and the genetic response to the environment.
在我的时空范围内所施加的冲击，以及基因对环境的反应。
That there are limits on which the system can
存在一些限制，在此之上系统可以进行
multiply, differentiate and it is there
增殖、分化，而正是在此
where there are traumas, which are shocks, which can cause profound differentiations
存在创伤，这些是冲击，它们可能引起分化
profound
深层的
in the system. So at some point
在系统中。因此，在某个时刻
we need to be able to recognize these patterns. And so we have
需要能够识别这些模式。因此我们有
references.
参考依据。
we will study to help the body restructure itself.
我们将进行研究，以帮助身体重塑结构。
Because it has this power within it,
因为它自身拥有这种力量，
you remember, we have this self-regulation.
你还记得吗，我们有这种自我调节能力。
If I put cells like that,
如果我这样放置细胞，
the environment around them,
它们周围的环境，
by growth systems,
通过生长系统，
the forces that will come around them,
作用于它们周围的力，
that will cause at some point
在某个时刻会引起
a cell division,
细胞分裂，
a cell multiplication.
细胞增殖。
For there to be differentiation,
为了发生分化，
the pressure must already be greater.
首先需要更大的压力。
in another environment. And so it's simply to explain that there is a difference
在另一个环境中。因此，这只是为了解释存在差异
between a multiplication and a multiplication with
在增殖与伴随
a differentiation. And that if at some point
分化的增殖之间。而且如果在某个时刻
the cell receives too strong a constraint, it dies.
细胞受到过强的应力，它就会死亡。
And we will see that the body
我们将看到身体
uses both to develop, to grow, processes,
同时用于发育、生长等过程，
it will multiply,
它会增殖，
where it will.
它将去往何处。
multiply and differentiate.
增殖并分化。
And in some cases, it will have what is called cell death,
在某些情况下，它会发生我们所说的细胞死亡，
which is called cellular apoptosis.
我们称之为细胞凋亡。
Here, I have a bunch of cells,
在这里，我有一团细胞，
and they receive too much constraint,
它们受到过大的应力，
mechanical compression constraint, for example.
例如，机械性压迫应力。
Well, what will remain is just a cellular exudate.
那么，剩下的就只是细胞渗出物。